One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I grabbed hold, digging in my claws
te ni totte tsume o tateta
but the future
sono mirai wa
blurred together, colors running
nijimu iro ni kasunde mieta
A red that can swallow even summer's hues
natsu no iro mo nuritsubusu you na aka ni
bokura no koe kakikesareteiku you de
now attempts to blot out our voices
Move those halting feet of yours
tachidomaru sono ashi o fumidasou ze
Don't let stand the lies for show
misekake no uso yarisugosu yori
I'll give up countless mornings for my vows
nandome no asa chikai to hikikaeru yo
For the dream that we shared
bokura ga miteita yume
Come In, World
Oimo! Kashii!
Brogy the Red Ogre
Captain of the Giant Pirate Crew
Get rid of those annoying ships!
Lead the soldiers to the right and left
and destroy the ships!
Dorry the Blue Ogre
Captain of the Giant Pirate Crew
Watch out for the cannonballs!
Got it, Captains!
Kashii, Giant Pirate Crew
Let's go, guys!
Oimo, Giant Pirate Crew
Where were they?!
The legendary Giant Pirate Crew itself has arrived!
We've confirmed the notorious Brogy the Red
and Dorry the Blue leading the crew!
Why would all these warriors
from back then be here on this island?!
The Giant Pirate Crew made landfall!
Shoot at and repel those damn Giants!
Go for it, boys!
We'll go ahead!
M...
Masters!
Why are they here?!
Master Brogy!
Master Dorry!
Even Oimo and Kashii are here!
I wonder if they brought those two
back from Little Garden.
Oimo! Kashii!
Yeah!
Even if we went to Elbaph,
I thought we wouldn't be able to see them!
A long time ago,
the world feared the Giant Pirate Crew,
but they disbanded due to a huge quarrel
between their two Captains, Dorry and Brogy.
Luffy and the others
stumbled into their century-long feud.
And on a different island,
they met Oimo and Kashii...
...who went to see
how their bosses were doing
and became friends.
They're clearly attacking the Marine ships!
I can't believe they are your friends!
They must've found out about this
and hurried here!
What? How?
This incident is a Government-related attack.
It'd be in the news by the next day.
Though I'm sure
they're reporting the Government favorably.
So this is a major story!
Yeah, it must be!
The masters didn't come here for war!
They came to help us escape!
Hurry up and get ready to go!
Brook, where are you now?
Why do I hear a scream?
Don't worry!
I'll be there soon with the Sunny!
You're the best!
Yeah, we'll be passing through in a moment.
Stop the ship!
Ouch!
If we fall off the island,
we'll hit the barrier and explode!
Hello? It's me, Lilith!
Listen, this bonehead
didn't think twice and...
It's quite an uproar.
We must at least be prepared
to escape any minute!
It's not the time to be fighting, Zoro.
You're so persistent! I'm in a hurry!
Only the one
who'll win at the end can say that.
Roronoa!
Besides, right now you’re the pain in the ass
for making your friends wait!
I’m not wrong, am I?
You guys are a bunch of idiots
who can't leave a single one of your crew behind.
As long as you're breathing,
your crewmates are trapped here.
You say that...
...as if you're in control of
how long we fight.
Rob Lucci!
What's the damage report on our ships?
About 30 small and medium vessels
have sunk!
And the numbers are rising!
Small and medium vessels, fall back!
Only warships, move forward!
We're getting nowhere like this!
Yes, Vice Admiral Red King!
Why do we have to attack our own weapons?!
Hey, Bonney!
Why are you crying?
Of course I'm crying, you idiot...
I've been looking for you!
I've been with you all this time!
But I didn't know that you were Nika!
Nika? What's that?
I've always been...
...wanting to throw
a rubber punch like you!
I remember seeing your weak little punch.
Then show me the real one!
Punch him...
...for Vegapunk!
What?! Vegapunk!
You foolish insects.
There is a reason you deserve to die.
No, there isn't.
Get us off the island!
All right, Bonney!
Let's do it!
And from now on,
throw a punch like this!
How could you hurt my friend?!
Gum-Gum...
...Dawn...
...Gatling!
We gotta get away on our own!
Come on, Bonney!
Use the hover function!
It allows you to fly low over the island.
Vegapunk! Come with us!
You go on ahead, Bonney...
I know quite a lot about medical science.
If I...
...move now,
I'll die.
What?!
You'll die even if you don't move.
Give up.
You've got to be kidding!
That was a laser beam!
Love is stronger than light!
If that were true,
physics as we know it would be dead.
All right, let's go!
It's the northeast coast, right?!
Yeah!
I'll lose face...
...if I don't at least
bring back your heads...
Just write a letter of apology.
My, my.
How the Five Elders have fallen.
I wonder what kind of power this is...
I've never heard of the Five Elders
personally descending to the lower world.
But it’s helped us quite a bit.
Okay, mission complete.
Why are you two here?
Catarina Devon, Captain of the Sixth Ship
Blackbeard Pirates (Dog-Dog Fruit,
Mythical Type, Model: Nine-Tailed Fox)
Van Augur, Captain of the Third Ship
Blackbeard Pirates (Warp-Warp Fruit)
Catarina Devon...
I never thought the savages from Level 6
would submit to someone.
Teach is special.
As is his bloodline.
Oh, you were aware of that?
You people are always making strange moves.
What are you really after?
The world.
All right. Let's go back.
We're still on the island.
Couldn't you warp us a little farther?
I'm still under training.
W...! W...!
W... Wait!
Please wait!
I didn't expect to see you here!
"Supersonic" Van Augur!
"The Crescent Moon Hunter" Catarina Devon!
I'm Caribou!
I'm a pirate! If I may be so bold!
I've been looking for you folks!
I set out to sea wishing to be like him!
My dream is to become
one of "Blackbeard" Teach-sama's men!
Please, I beg you!
Let me see him for a moment!
What?!
Wait, wait! Please wait!
Who is this guy?
Wet-Haired Caribou...
That's right!
Just hold your fire, please!
He is a pirate,
but this is a Government island.
The commodore has many assassins after him.
I'm absolutely not one of them!
Believe me!
If you guys kill me now,
Teach-sama will bash your heads in!
Oh... Why?
B-Because I've got information
that no one else has!
They're the Ancient Weapons named after gods
that existed a long time ago.
One of them, Poseidon,
refers to the power of
Princess Shirahoshi of Fish-Man Island.
And another one, Pluton,
lies beneath the Land of Wano.
The terrifying Ancient Weapons are
said to have the power to destroy the world.
The Straw Hats and I are probably...
...the only ones in this world
who know where the two of them are.
If you let me meet Teach-sama,
I'll give you all the information I have!
I'm sure it'll make him happy!
So please take me to him!
I'll definitely be useful to you!
All ships! Get away from the coast!
Vice Admiral Doberman
Don't fight the Pacifistas!
Damn! The Bubble Shield again!
Why do we have to be reminded of
the power of the Special Science Group?!
Fighting them doesn't excite us!
A win is a loss, and a loss is an injustice!
Vice Admiral Bluegrass
The Giants made landfall
on the other side of the island!
Vice Admiral Urban
A series of unexpected events is happening!
Could the Buster Call be called off?
That would be unprecedented.
Vice Admiral Hound
Vice Admiral Guillotine
Vegapunk was the one who gave a pirate power over the Pacifistas!
Calling it off is not an option!
He's a complete traitor to the Government!
A major offender!
To turn things around,
we need to take back the Pacifistas!
Take out the pirate Jewelry Bonney!
Vice admirals! Leave your position
and eliminate Jewelry Bonney!
She's currently moving away
from the center of the Fabriophase...
...to the northeast coast!
I repeat!
Eliminate Jewelry Bonney!
Got it!
This is Tosa. Target confirmed!
Marine HQ
Vice Admiral Tosa
I'll get close and execute the order!
These claws are ten Finger Pistols
that will even shred armor!
What?!
Tosa Bite!
Why are the Giants here on this island?!
We're in a hurry,
but now we have more enemies?!
Who are you guys?
I researched the new members
on their wanted posters,
but I don't recognize any of you.
Are you lab workers from this island?
We're here for the Straw Hats!
Luffy is our captain...
What do you have against him?!
No, we have nothing against him,
just gratitude!
We're Elbaph warriors!
If you're their friends,
we'll protect you at all costs!
Come on! You scared me!
Our bad, sorry!
Luffy, Sanji, and Vegapunk
are still at the center of the island!
Will you help them?!
Those names bring back memories!
Of course we will!
Thanks!
Vegapunk is supposed to be the man
that scholar was talking about.
Yeah.
Take them to the ship!
Will do!
Let's hurry on!
The fire has spread quite a bit!
Okay, Bosses!
Leave everything to those two.
You don't have to worry about a thing.
Are they the ones that
Usopp calls his masters all the time?
Tosa's communication is cut off.
He got beaten in a counterattack?
Or he ran into a Giant?
Vice Admiral Pomsky
I'm going onto the island!
I'll attack from the sea!
Hop on, Doll!
There is an Elbaph ship
on the northeast coast.
The strength of the Giants varies greatly.
Have you ever fought them?
More than two decades ago,
I had a Giant as a boss.
“Had”...?
You mean Saul?
He was a strong one.
Where are the rest of your crew members?
They're at a lab above the clouds.
Above the clouds? Is it a Sky Island?
No.
It's right there.
That's the one.
You're not gonna make it
if you don't beat it!
Ow, ow, ow!
I'll bleed if I move!
Old Man Apple!
We promised you
we'd help you escape from the island!
I know I asked for that, but...
...now I’ve made up my mind!
There is something here that I must protect.
I wanted to tell Bonney...
...about her authority
when she was a little older...
Her life is inevitably in danger...
Please keep her safe...
You look much less human now.
You've got an insane look in your eyes.
Are you coated with poison or something?
Look out, Luffy!
Sanji!
Get the old man outta here!
Don't worry if it hurts to move him!
Okay!
Come on! Come on!
Ow, ow, ow...
Hey! That's enough, Sanji!
Just be still!
What?!
No!
Vegapunk!
Old Man Apple!
Sanji! Run!
To the back of the island!
Dammit!
I'm sorry, Vegapunk!
You bastards...
...aren't going anywhere!
What's wrong, Vegapunk?
Stay with me!
Dammit!
Hey! Vegapunk!
Are you dead?!
Hey! Why are you smiling?!
Um... Hello?
Check, check.
Come in! Come in, world!
I'm Dr. Vegapunk.
I'm a humble genius scientist.
The message I'm about to leave
will likely shock everyone,
but it is...
...the truth of this world!
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop beep-beep-beep-bup-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipii pipopii, pipopiipii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep
Piipapii papipo, piipapii
No No No No No norenai
No, no, no, no, no, not feelin' it
kobiritsuichatte mou odorenai
I'm all stiff, all outta dances
My head feels so good, 'f I get unlucky again
atama Feel so good, mata Unlucky demo
Cola de fukitobase yowaki o
just gonna blow away the shy with a cola
Hey all you boys & girls! Looking good!
soko no Boys & Girls! omae ii yatsu
Hey all you boys & girls!
soko no Boys & Girls!
Update failed. I've had enough!
appudeto wa shippai kori gori
Wasn't it OK 'til yesterday?
kinou made nara seikai?
La la la la la la, run, run, run...
ran ran ran ran ran ran Run Run Run
"Hiding yet?"
mou ii kai?
You ready yet, up for a dance
junbi wa douyo odoreru no?
bukkowareteru kono jidai
in this broken era?
"Come find us!"
mou ii yo!
Spread out from here, drop into the world
koko kara kakusan sekai e Drop
Let loose on the stage of freedom and liberation
jiyuu to kaihou no Stage e
Those rising heads're punks!!!!!! No way!!!
wakiagaru atama ga Punk!!!!!! No way!!!
Sick of waitin', goof off and dance
matenaiyo fuzaketa Dance
Dopamine spilling over
afuredasu dopamin
The lonely singing in unity
kodoku ga tsudoi utau koushin
Bip-bip-bip-bup-bup-bup-bup-bupping
pipipi papapapapatteru
Can't can't can't count me out yet
mada mada mada horobinai
There's some stranger waving me over
shiranai dareka ga temaneki da
Smilin' so wide that it can't be real
uso mitai ni waratteru